Write a quick summary of what we've covered in this section.
We've covered lists and why you have lists and lists are very important for life.
And we looked at how you can create a list quite simply by defining whatever your list name is, and
then in square brackets listing all the items that are going to be in that list.
You can print your list and access the list simply by using the index number.
Remembering it always starts at zero.
So why we need list zero, one, two and three?
And it's as simple as that.
And so when we run that we produce a list of what's inside the list.
So lists are really cool.
We also looked at tuples.
Tuples are exactly the same.
All we do is if we change from those square brackets to the curly brackets, all of a sudden that list
cannot change.
So in this example everything's going to continue much the same because we're not trying to change anything.
But that list will give you an assignment error if you try and change something in it afterwards.
So lists and tuples they're very convenient way to store things that are similar and need to be worked
with in groups.
As we said a list of friends and maybe it's months of the year or maybe it's tax table values.
Whatever it may be, storing them in a list is very powerful, and we'll see later on how you can use
them.
So that is lists.
And we leave it over to you to list all your needs and wants and have as much fun as you possibly can.
Programming in Python.